Hello everyone.
Welcome back.
So, in today's video, I'm going to share a tool with you all.
It's perfect for taking one of our videos,
to replace the audio.
So, let's take a look.
So, here's what the project looks like once you get inside.
It's trained on a local large language model.
and it's been turned into a tool.
Alright, so the first thing we can do is upload our own media.
and choose to upload a local file.
So, let's just click on this upload button.
For example, I can just grab any video I have here.
And then, let's just go ahead and upload this.
And just like that, our media is uploaded.
Of course, for those of you whose videos are on Bilibili or YouTube,
So, you can just use the links from Bilibili and YouTube directly.
Just copy it over.
and that'll import the video as well.
So, for example, let's say we're right here.
Let's take a video I recorded for you all earlier,
Let's take this video for example.
Alright, so let's just copy this link.
Or, you can just copy the share link.
the share link.
And then, just paste it right in here.
And just like that, you're all set.
We'll click submit.
And it will automatically pull in the video for you.
and then download it.
And it's not just limited to YouTube.
It also supports Bilibili.
All you have to do is copy the link for the Bilibili video as well.
and you're good to go.
So, for example, let's say we have a video right here.
So, we'll just go ahead and click on 'Share'.
And then a link will pop up right here.
Alright, we're going to take this link. Now, pay close attention, you absolutely need this link.
Make sure there's no Chinese characters at the beginning.
So, just go ahead and paste that link right here.
Alright, so right now, it's downloading the video.
Alright, so we just have to wait for this download to finish.
And just like that, the video is fed into the system as an input.
So, this process is basically like grabbing it from a video website.
to download the video.
And it's the same for Bilibili.
So for Bilibili, you just go ahead and paste the link right here.
And then, you can go ahead and download it.
Up top, we have the video.
And down here is the audio.
So, that's the first step.
So basically, you're just importing the media file.
So, whether you're importing media from your local files,
or even importing from video websites, both work just fine.
Alright, for the second step...
So, right here, we need to get it transcribed.
Since my video is in Chinese,
So, the media language selected here is the default, which is CHINESE.
Now, if your video is in another language,
So you can just switch it right here.
Alright, so for the second step, we're going to need to click on this 'Transcribe' button.
So, we'll click on 'Transcribe'.
So, 'transcribe' basically means you're starting the model.
and then extract the video's content and its subtitles.
So, once the transcription is done,
So, we can take a look at the result after this transcription.
We can also run a translation on it.
So, the correct workflow is: first, you upload your video right here.
or, you know, just copy the video's link.
And then, click 'Submit'.
So, the second step is transcription, right?
Then, for the third step, if you need to translate the video,
So you can use this translation feature.
Here, you can set the original language and the target language we want.
and set it up.
Alright, so down here we have a few voice options.
And this one is using the free voice function, by the way.
There are quite a few beta features available here.
And on top of that,
We've also included one more thing, which is...
And this 'voice' section has a ton of, uh, well-known public figures.
For instance, let's scroll down and take a look.
So, these are mostly in English, right?
For example, in English, you have Donald Trump's voice.
And there's Elon Musk's.
Voice.
And you can see his avatar right below it.
This one's from Iran.
And then we can also, for example, choose the Donald Trump voice we just saw.
Okay, so this one is in English.
Of course, sometimes you might not need to do the translation either.
All you have to do is switch the language.
So, you can just select Chinese.
Inside, you'll find voices like Jolin Tsai's, Dilraba's,
Dilraba's, Li Yifeng's...
Kris Wu,
the voices of Yang Mi and Zhao Liying.
Alright, so this step is the final one, which is the synthesis.
So, what 'synthesize' means is that after you've done the transcription here,
We can take the output video and use Dilraba's voice for it.
Or, say, Elon Musk's voice.
or, say, replace it with Donald Trump's voice.
And with that, you can...
So, what's the end result?
So, let's say you have a product you want to launch globally.
So, you recorded it in Chinese.
So, you can use this method.
First, you'll need to transcribe it.
After you've transcribed it, you'll need to translate the Chinese into English, right?
So, once you've got the English translation,
Then you're gonna need a foreign voice actor.
and then you can record their voice, right?
That would be perfect!
So you can take this Chinese video...
into an English one.
Alright, so you can see the video right here.
Alright, the transcription is done.
And here are the Chinese subtitles.
Alright, so for the next step, we can have it translate the Chinese text into English.
Alright, the translation is done now.
And here are the translated subtitles.
And then, we can also open up the video and take a closer look.
This is still the original Chinese audio.
But now, with the English subtitles added.
That's because the video originally had its own subtitles built-in.
Alright, let's take a look now.
Alright, let's switch to a different voice for this English part.
From Elon Musk...
We can just switch to another one, uh...
Let's just pick one at random here.
Let's go with this one.
Let's hear what his voice sounds like.
I'm simple.
Alright, let's hit 'synthesize'.
So at this point, it's going to take this person's voice and...
and embed it right into the video.
So, what this means is, if your original video...
So, if you don't have subtitles here,
So, it can also help you with this video,
generate the subtitles for you.
and then translate it into English.
And finally, let's use a foreigner's voice.
And then just replace the original audio with it.
Of course, first off, you'll see there are some celebrity voices here.
Here's Naruto's voice.
But for now, you guys do need to be mindful of the copyright issues.
So, you might be wondering if there are any copyright issues with using these voices.
So, the one I'd recommend is the EDGE TTS.
So, for the voices in here,
These are all completely free to use.
They are not licensed for copyright.
So, for some of the voices in this Coy Voice tool...
So, if you guys want to use it,
So you still need to be mindful of the copyright issues.
But if you're just doing it for a demonstration,
Actually, it doesn't really matter, but this process can take a while.
Alright, let's take another look.
So let's click on this translation button.
So, if you have some, uh, subtitles,
You can upload your subtitles right here.
and then use the translation feature right here.
And of course, you can also use the AI translation feature.
So, all we have to do is enter our own API key right here.
This is the token from their platform.
Copy the token.
And then paste it right here.
And then, right here, it will automatically load our API.
as well as some models available on the platform.
So you can just go ahead and make your choice.
So, for example, right here, you can select models from the cloud.
GEMINI's model,
and OpenAI's models.
and even the DeepSeek model.
You can choose any of them right here.
So, when it comes to the translation part,
So, if you feel that this...
If the translation from the local model isn't quite up to par,
So you can also use this AI to do the translation, right?
That way, you can really bump up the quality a notch.
Okay.
So, for this project of ours,
Alright, so that's a quick rundown of the basics.
So, once this part is done processing,
Let me give you another quick demo.
Let's check out the final voice-over result.
So, besides that,
So, let's take a look at this project.
This project is called Video to Speech.
We haven't made it available on any open-source platforms, by the way.
So, the only way for you to get it is by joining our community.
to get your hands on this project.
So, for our beginner users,
So for those of you who are complete beginners,
So, for now, they can only join the beginners' group chat first.
You at least need to get familiar with Codex Cloud,
Or, you could just learn a thing or two about our agent system.
Then you can...
and you can apply to join our agent community.
And of course, joining the group is completely free for everyone.
So, make sure you don't get roped into paying by some other people.
All of these are completely free and open for everyone.
But the problem is, a lot of people just don't know what they're doing.
and then they just have a ton of questions.
So, to help improve the quality of the videos,
So, we've decided to raise the bar a bit.
And getting it up and running is also super simple.
Alright everyone, just double-click on this 'start' file.
And with that .bat file, you're all set to start it up.
Alright, so let's just wait for this project to finish running.
On top of that, let me share something else with you.
So, everyone can go through our API site,
specifically within our Deep Cloud Creation Technology platform.
Once you're on this API distribution site,
and get our own token.
So, where can we use this?
One way is to use it with what we've shared with you before,
within Codex Cloud.
It can also be...
Or, you can hook it up to our Immersive Translation tool.
and connect it to the Immersive Translate plugin.
And then, you can go ahead and translate the webpage.
Right here, you can go ahead and enter your own API key.
Select the OpenAI compatible mode.
And then you can go ahead and click 'Test' right here.
And if the test is successful,
And you'll see a green arrow appear right here.
And for this next one, the custom interface address...
Just make sure it's the same as what I have here, and you'll be all set.
So this is a...
And there's one more thing.
So, we can connect this to our agent system.
And for our agent system, all you need to do is copy this token.
And then, get the model list.
And right here, it's going to list out a whole bunch of models for you.
so you can go ahead and integrate them.
And over here, you'll see the models you've already connected.
For example, here are the models I've already connected.
So, what if I want to connect other models here?
So I can also just go ahead and connect one right here.
For example, let's connect the latest version of the Cloud model.
Click 'Import'.
And then we'll be automatically brought to this page.
Let's go with Cloud.
Then, you can go ahead and bump up the context length a bit.
These are usually the 1-million-token models.
So, one million tokens for the context.
And then, we just click 'Confirm'.
And just like that, we're all set.
So, all we need to do is switch over to Cloud.
Now, let's add the model we just set up and click 'Enable'.
And now, in the list of available models, we'll see a new one: Cloud Office.
This is version 4-88 of the model.
So this is another way it can be integrated.
Alright, so that was just a quick recap for everyone.
So, how do we get this thing to work?
within the realm of, uh, various agents, or rather, the whole field of AI.
including translation software,
And now, we're also adding this kind of video processing tool.
And then we have productivity tools like Codex and Cloud.
And now, we've also added this video tool, right?
a tool for video, or rather, voice generation.
So in this area, we're seeing a pretty significant improvement.
And later on, for example, these processing models here...
and they all run on your local computing power.
As you can see, this is my local computing power right here.
In fact, it can be maxed out completely.
So, the better your graphics card is,
the faster your processing speed will be.
So, for that reason, I'd really recommend using a Windows device for this.
So, for this local project,
And it works pretty well even when you're offline.
And once the whole project is up and running,
And it doesn't consume any API credits, by the way.
And it's completely free and open-source.
Alright, let's wait for this process to finish, and then I'll break down the results for you.
Alright, the video has finished synthesizing.
Alright, let's take a look.
Today, we're diving into the world of scientific research.
This time,
This one's a bit more hardcore, with two projects in total.
And I've pushed them to GitHub.
So everyone can configure them.
Whether you're using Codex,
Cloud Code, or some other smart system.
You can go ahead and configure it.
And here's a little reminder.
Alright.
Alright, so that's a wrap for this project.
Alright, let's go ahead and launch it.
So, let's go ahead and close this page for now.
Alright, so let's head into the Video to Speech section.
So, that's the file we just generated.
in this workspace.
It's right here in our workspace.
Let's take a look.
And this is the video we downloaded from YouTube.
And this is the result from the translation.
And this is what we have here.
This is a video I downloaded from Bilibili earlier.
And then, there are different channels for that.
So the videos it downloads will be different, you see.
And then I did some translation work.
And all those results will be right here in this workspace.
And you can see the final result after the replacement is done. Alright.
So that's what the workspace is for.
Alright, let's take a look at how to start it up.
All we have to do is double-click this 'start.bat' file.
And as you can see, it's going to tell us right here.
So, it's because we had one running just now.
So, it needs to shut down that process first.
And then restart the project.
It's called Video to Speech.
Now, let's wait for the project to launch.
So, for the first time you launch it,
you'll need to install some dependencies and set up the environment.
But usually, you just need to double-click the app, and that's it.
So, once it's up and running,
and it will automatically take you to the interface we just saw.
Alright, so our project has launched successfully.
It's just like what we saw a moment ago.
Alright.
And that's what I want to share with you all in this video.
a tool for converting video audio.
So, you can all go ahead and check it out.
and use it right on your local computer.
Thank you all.